Contact

malicksabih@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/muhammadsabih-ur-rehman-507738216 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)
Dart
JavaScript

Certifications

Introduction to Programming Using JavaScript

Certified Digital Marketing

Introduction to Programming Using Python

Programming Foundations: Fundamentals

Certified Freelancing

Muhammad Sabih Ur Rehman

Computer System Engineer | Data Science Enthusiast | Android Developer | Front End Developer | Web Developer Karāchi

Summary

I'm known as Sabih Mallick, I am 19 years old and currently living in Karachi, Pakistan.

If I can share one thing about myself it would be that I am fiery and love challenging myself. I embrace it when people tell me I cannot do something and generally hit harder when hit.

I do not firmly believe in horoscopes, but I can say I find interest in how they define TAURUS the same as I see myself.

A reliable, easy-going, passionate in recruiting and talking to people. I am a determined student-driven by setting and getting goals. Currently, I'm a Sophomore at NED University of Engineering and Technology doing undergrads in Computer and information systems engineering. Also, I participated in many extra-circular activities such as karate, gymnastics, English plays, International Math Kangaroo Competition, athletics, football, and futsal inter-school tournaments. I captained my futsal side to several tournaments. I suppose my top Tier interest is ultimately Health & Well-being. Without your health and well-being, you ain't got nothing. I am keen on learning more about Data Science, Artificial Intelligence, and Cyber Security,

Experience

Fiverr

1 month

Freelance Web Developer March 2022 - Present (1 month)

Freelance Software Engineer March 2022 - Present (1 month)

Education

NED University of Engineering and Technology

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Science · (2020 - 2024)